domain,text,entities
technology,Marissa Mayer announced a new edge computing at SpaceX.,"[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Apple released a quantum computing that improves edge computing.,"[('Apple', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show battle happened in Rome, Italy around 1664-06-18.",[]
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from Congress in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss policy announcement.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
science,Max Planck Institute announced a particle discovery that impacts genetics.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on particle discovery led by Isaac Newton was published on 1991-04-05.,"[('1991', 'DATE'), ('Isaac Newton', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Cristiano Ronaldo led Wimbledon to victory at the season opener in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"George Washington Carver led trials of yield improvement study in Punjab, India.","[('George Washington Carver', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel met leaders from Parliament in New Delhi, India to discuss policy announcement.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding healthcare at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"CIMMYT introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Iowa, USA.","[('CIMMYT', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Leonardo da Vinci premiered a symphony at Vienna, Austria.",[]
sports,"M.S. Dhoni led Wimbledon to victory at the season opener in London, UK.","[('UK', 'ORG')]"
science,CERN announced a field research that impacts biology.,"[('CERN', 'ORG')]"
business,"Tesla opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand manufacturing.",[]
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in robotics was reported by Apple.,"[('Apple', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Iowa, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a particle discovery in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from United Nations in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding trade at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
sports,FC Barcelona announced a new tournament for 2024-2025.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
technology,Sundar Pichai announced a new quantum computing at SpaceX.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON')]"
science,CERN announced a field research that impacts climatology.,"[('CERN', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Vincent van Gogh premiered a exhibition at Madrid, Spain.",[]
science,A study on particle discovery led by Jane Goodall was published on 1500-11-03.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON')]"
business,"Samsung opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand manufacturing.","[('South Korea', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Intel released a robotics that improves 5G networks.,[]
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Tesla.,[]
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"M. S. Swaminathan led trials of pest control trial in Lima, Peru.",[]
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from Parliament in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
arts,"A famous opera by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Tate Modern in Madrid, Spain.","[('Tate Modern', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Satya Nadella led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Silicon Valley, USA.","[('Satya Nadella', 'PERSON'), ('Silicon Valley', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a field research in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"International Rice Research Institute introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Punjab, India.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on climate study led by Albert Einstein was published on 1771-02-18.,"[('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Wangari Maathai led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Lima, Peru.","[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",[]
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
sports,NBA announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
agriculture,"M. S. Swaminathan led trials of yield improvement study in Punjab, India.",[]
arts,"Pablo Picasso premiered a painting at Madrid, Spain.","[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The battle took place in Delhi, India and involved Roman Senate.","[('Roman Senate', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Leonardo da Vinci is housed in Metropolitan Opera in New York, USA.","[('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A policy announcement was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.","[('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The uprising took place in Versailles, France and involved Allied Powers.","[('Allied Powers', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The season opener in London, UK featured Lionel Messi and NBA.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show uprising happened in Berlin, Germany around 1539-09-02.",[]
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from Parliament in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss summit.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
science,NASA announced a field research that impacts genetics.,"[('NASA', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on particle discovery led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1538-06-17.,"[('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON')]"
business,Siemens acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by European Union impacting New Delhi, India.","[('European Union', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
science,"Researchers at CERN reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.","[('CERN', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Sydney Opera House announced restoration of the painting in New York, USA.","[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show expedition happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1757-05-31.",[]
sports,"The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and Wimbledon.",[]
history,Julius Caesar was a key figure in the Treaty signing.,"[('Julius Caesar', 'PERSON')]"
technology,SpaceX released a robotics that improves 5G networks.,[]
history,"Records show battle happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1549-02-10.",[]
science,Max Planck Institute announced a particle discovery that impacts climatology.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show coronation happened in Rome, Italy around 1988-08-07.","[('1988', 'DATE')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Lima, Peru adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by ICAR.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The season opener in London, UK featured Serena Williams and FC Barcelona.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Norman Borlaug led trials of yield improvement study in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
history,"Records show coronation happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1821-08-26.",[]
arts,Beyoncé exhibited a new exhibition at Tate Modern.,"[('Tate Modern', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by OpenAI.,[]
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2024-2025.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
arts,"Beyoncé premiered a exhibition at Vienna, Austria.",[]
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the merger.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Lionel Messi and NBA.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Norman Borlaug led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Iowa, USA.","[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Sydney Opera House announced restoration of the opera in Madrid, Spain.","[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in AI-driven sensors was reported by Apple.,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the Treaty signing.,"[('Mahatma Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of pest control trial for soybeans.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
business,Samsung acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $15M.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.,[]
agriculture,"Wangari Maathai led trials of pest control trial in Iowa, USA.","[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,merger led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in robotics was reported by SpaceX.,[]
sports,Wimbledon announced a new final match for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
sports,"The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and Wimbledon.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
science,Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at NASA.,"[('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at NASA reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.","[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google released a 5G networks that improves robotics.,"[('Google', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Rachel Carson showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.,"[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Ada Lovelace led the launch of a quantum computing in London, UK.","[('Ada Lovelace', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
business,"Siemens opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand cloud services.",[]
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Grace Hopper announced a new 5G networks at Apple.,"[('Grace Hopper', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the IPO.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG'), ('IPO', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",[]
business,Tim Cook became CEO of Samsung following the IPO.,"[('Tim Cook', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG'), ('IPO', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by AgriTech Ltd.",[]
history,Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the battle.,"[('Mahatma Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
history,"Records show uprising happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1537-02-18.",[]
science,CERN announced a particle discovery that impacts genetics.,"[('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
science,Jane Goodall published findings on field research at CERN.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"ICAR introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
business,Reliance Industries acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $450M.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the merger.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A policy announcement was passed by European Union impacting Washington, USA.","[('European Union', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"ICAR introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"International Rice Research Institute introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Lima, Peru.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of pest control trial for soybeans.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Satya Nadella led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Shenzhen, China.","[('Satya Nadella', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a quantum computing in Bengaluru, India.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Tim Berners-Lee announced a new 5G networks at Google.,"[('Tim Berners', 'PERSON'), ('Google', 'ORG')]"
science,Rosalind Franklin published findings on climate study at Max Planck Institute.,"[('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON'), ('Institute', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on climate study led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1980-12-14.,"[('1980', 'DATE'), ('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous painting by Ludwig van Beethoven is housed in Metropolitan Opera in Paris, France.","[('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Lima, Peru.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Punjab, India adopted yield improvement study developed by International Rice Research Institute.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from European Union in Washington, USA to discuss summit.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('European Union', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Grace Hopper announced a new AI-driven sensors at Intel.,"[('Grace Hopper', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Pablo Picasso premiered a symphony at Paris, France.","[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON')]"
science,A study on gene sequencing led by Jane Goodall was published on 1749-01-26.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON')]"
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Samsung following the merger.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Sundar Pichai led the launch of a quantum computing in Stockholm, Sweden.","[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel met leaders from European Union in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON'), ('European Union', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON')]"
sports,FC Barcelona announced a new final match for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by ICAR.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by CIMMYT.","[('CIMMYT', 'ORG')]"
business,Mary Barra became CEO of Samsung following the acquisition.,"[('Mary Barra', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in London, UK.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on particle discovery at CERN.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
science,Harvard University announced a gene sequencing that impacts physics.,"[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
history,"The Treaty signing took place in Berlin, Germany and involved Mughal Empire.","[('The Treaty', 'PERSON'), ('Mughal Empire', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
business,Reliance Industries acquired Goldman Sachs in a deal valued at $450M.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
business,"Reliance Industries opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand cloud services.","[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Pablo Picasso premiered a installation at Paris, France.","[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a climate study in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
science,Jane Goodall published findings on field research at NASA.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The battle marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
technology,SpaceX released a edge computing that improves quantum computing.,[]
history,Nelson Mandela was a key figure in the expedition.,"[('Nelson Mandela', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and Wimbledon.",[]
technology,Grace Hopper announced a new 5G networks at Apple.,"[('Grace Hopper', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
history,"The Treaty signing marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.","[('The Treaty', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON')]"
business,Siemens acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by SpaceX.,[]
agriculture,"Farmers in Punjab, India adopted yield improvement study developed by ICAR.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
science,CERN announced a gene sequencing that impacts genetics.,"[('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on field research led by Marie Curie was published on 1882-10-03.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding healthcare at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a quantum computing in Silicon Valley, USA.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('Silicon Valley', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by Parliament impacting New Delhi, India.","[('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The coronation took place in Berlin, Germany and involved Ottoman Empire.","[('Ottoman Empire', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Punjab, India.",[]
science,NASA announced a field research that impacts biology.,"[('NASA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The coronation marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
sports,"The final match in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and NBA.","[('UK', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.","[('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Tesla acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $15M.,[]
history,"The coronation marked a turning point in Constantinople, Turkey's history.",[]
technology,Marissa Mayer announced a new robotics at Apple.,"[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
business,"Goldman Sachs opened a new office in New York, USA to expand consumer electronics.","[('New York', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by AgriTech Ltd.",[]
history,"The Treaty signing marked a turning point in Constantinople, Turkey's history.","[('The Treaty', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Serena Williams led Wimbledon to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON')]"
business,Jamie Dimon became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.,"[('Jamie Dimon', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Lima, Peru.",[]
history,"Records show coronation happened in Delhi, India around 1841-04-20.",[]
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of pest control trial in Iowa, USA.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by European Union impacting Geneva, Switzerland.","[('European Union', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new final match for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
sports,"The final match in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and Wimbledon.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous opera by Pablo Picasso is housed in Sydney Opera House in Madrid, Spain.","[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The season opener in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and FC Barcelona.","[('UK', 'ORG'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The final match in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and NBA.","[('NBA', 'ORG')]"
science,CERN announced a climate study that impacts genetics.,"[('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,Isaac Newton published findings on field research at CERN.,"[('Isaac Newton', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,Max Planck Institute announced a field research that impacts climatology.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by OpenAI.,[]
agriculture,A study by George Washington Carver showed benefits of yield improvement study for soybeans.,"[('George Washington Carver', 'PERSON')]"
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the restructuring.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Grace Hopper led the launch of a 5G networks in Stockholm, Sweden.","[('Grace Hopper', 'PERSON')]"
business,Siemens acquired Samsung in a deal valued at $1.2B.,[]
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.","[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new season opener for 2024-2025.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from United Nations in New Delhi, India to discuss policy announcement.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A policy announcement was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",[]
science,"Researchers at CERN reported a climate study in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding education at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The expedition marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.",[]
business,Goldman Sachs acquired Siemens in a deal valued at $1.2B.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show uprising happened in Delhi, India around 1726-07-15.",[]
business,merger led to restructuring at Tesla.,[]
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding climate at New Delhi, India.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
business,Samsung acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $450M.,[]
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by Intel.,[]
business,acquisition led to restructuring at Siemens.,[]
technology,Elon Musk announced a new edge computing at IBM.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('IBM', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Samsung.,[]
history,"The coronation took place in Rome, Italy and involved British Empire.","[('British Empire', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
business,"Samsung opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand financial services.",[]
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from Parliament in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss bill passage.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"FAO introduced a pest control trial to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('FAO', 'ORG')]"
business,Jamie Dimon became CEO of Tesla following the IPO.,"[('Jamie Dimon', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG'), ('IPO', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.","[('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.,[]
agriculture,"FAO introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Iowa, USA.","[('FAO', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new final match for 2024-2025.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding trade at Washington, USA.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and NBA.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
business,Tesla acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $450M.,[]
business,"Samsung opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand manufacturing.",[]
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in AI-driven sensors was reported by Apple.,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"George Washington Carver led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('George Washington Carver', 'PERSON')]"
science,NASA announced a climate study that impacts biology.,"[('NASA', 'ORG')]"
sports,"Lionel Messi led NBA to victory at the final match in London, UK.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,acquisition led to restructuring at Tesla.,[]
business,"Samsung opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand cloud services.",[]
science,A study on climate study led by Isaac Newton was published on 1683-02-14.,"[('Isaac Newton', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The tournament in Melbourne, Australia featured M.S. Dhoni and FC Barcelona.","[('FC', 'ORG')]"
sports,"M.S. Dhoni led Team India to victory at the season opener in Madrid, Spain.","[('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Marissa Mayer led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Shenzhen, China.","[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
science,Rosalind Franklin published findings on particle discovery at Harvard University.,"[('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Siemens.,[]
arts,"A famous installation by Ludwig van Beethoven is housed in Tate Modern in New York, USA.","[('Tate Modern', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The final match in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and Team India.","[('Team India', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
sports,Team India announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.","[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show uprising happened in Versailles, France around 1717-08-11.",[]
technology,"Elon Musk led the launch of a quantum computing in London, UK.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Cambridge, UK.","[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Sundar Pichai led the launch of a 5G networks in Silicon Valley, USA.","[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Silicon Valley', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the IPO.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG'), ('IPO', 'ORG')]"
history,"The battle marked a turning point in Versailles, France's history.",[]
history,Queen Elizabeth I was a key figure in the expedition.,"[('Queen Elizabeth', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A policy announcement was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in quantum computing was reported by IBM.,"[('IBM', 'ORG')]"
science,Harvard University announced a climate study that impacts biology.,"[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,acquisition led to restructuring at Samsung.,[]
technology,"Sundar Pichai led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.","[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON')]"
history,"Records show battle happened in Delhi, India around 1750-10-07.",[]
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a gene sequencing in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show Treaty signing happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1622-01-17.",[]
business,"Siemens opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand consumer electronics.",[]
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss bill passage.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Mary Barra became CEO of Siemens following the merger.,"[('Mary Barra', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
sports,Team India announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Ludwig van Beethoven exhibited a new exhibition at Sydney Opera House.,"[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Louvre Museum in Vienna, Austria.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
business,Mary Barra became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.,"[('Mary Barra', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('NASA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for rice.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
business,merger led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,"Tesla opened a new office in New York, USA to expand manufacturing.","[('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
arts,Pablo Picasso exhibited a new painting at Tate Modern.,"[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('Tate Modern', 'PERSON')]"
business,Reliance Industries acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Pablo Picasso exhibited a new painting at Metropolitan Opera.,"[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Ludwig van Beethoven premiered a exhibition at Madrid, Spain.",[]
history,"The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
technology,Marissa Mayer announced a new quantum computing at Intel.,"[('Marissa Mayer', 'PERSON')]"
business,Jamie Dimon became CEO of Siemens following the acquisition.,"[('Jamie Dimon', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
science,Max Planck Institute announced a climate study that impacts biology.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
history,"The uprising marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.",[]
arts,"Louvre Museum announced restoration of the painting in Paris, France.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
science,Isaac Newton published findings on field research at NASA.,"[('Isaac Newton', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
sports,"Lionel Messi led Wimbledon to victory at the final match in London, UK.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
history,"Records show coronation happened in Versailles, France around 1515-11-09.",[]
technology,IBM released a AI-driven sensors that improves AI-driven sensors.,"[('IBM', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
history,"The coronation took place in Constantinople, Turkey and involved British Empire.","[('British Empire', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by International Rice Research Institute.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Louvre Museum announced restoration of the symphony in Paris, France.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Tim Berners-Lee led the launch of a robotics in Bengaluru, India.","[('Tim Berners', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Serena Williams led Wimbledon to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON')]"
science,A study on particle discovery led by Marie Curie was published on 1912-08-20.,"[('1912', 'DATE'), ('Marie Curie', 'PERSON')]"
science,Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at CERN.,"[('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"M. S. Swaminathan led trials of yield improvement study in Iowa, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,IPO led to restructuring at Samsung.,"[('IPO', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on climate study led by Isaac Newton was published on 1537-01-31.,"[('Isaac Newton', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi met leaders from Parliament in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted pest control trial developed by ICAR.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Grace Hopper led the launch of a robotics in Silicon Valley, USA.","[('Grace Hopper', 'PERSON'), ('Silicon Valley', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
arts,Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new exhibition at Royal Academy.,"[('Royal Academy', 'PERSON')]"
science,Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at CERN.,"[('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on field research at Harvard University.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"ICAR introduced a pest control trial to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
history,Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the coronation.,"[('Mahatma Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The battle marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
history,"Records show uprising happened in Delhi, India around 1577-11-19.",[]
sports,"Cristiano Ronaldo led NBA to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and NBA.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Royal Academy announced restoration of the symphony in Vienna, Austria.","[('Royal Academy', 'PERSON')]"
business,"Reliance Industries opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand financial services.","[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('South Korea', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk announced a new robotics at Intel.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Cristiano Ronaldo led NBA to victory at the final match in London, UK.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and NBA.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Ada Lovelace led the launch of a 5G networks in Bengaluru, India.","[('Ada Lovelace', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Congress impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",[]
politics,"A summit was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.","[('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Frida Kahlo is housed in Metropolitan Opera in New York, USA.","[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON'), ('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by OpenAI.,[]
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of yield improvement study for wheat.,[]
business,Jamie Dimon became CEO of Reliance Industries following the IPO.,"[('Jamie Dimon', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG'), ('IPO', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in robotics was reported by SpaceX.,[]
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting New Delhi, India.","[('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for soybeans.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and Team India.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new painting at Sydney Opera House.,"[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for maize.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
business,restructuring led to restructuring at Samsung.,[]
technology,A breakthrough in robotics was reported by Microsoft.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
business,"Siemens opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand financial services.","[('South Korea', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.,"[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Team India announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Barack Obama met leaders from European Union in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss policy announcement.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('European Union', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The battle marked a turning point in Rome, Italy's history.",[]
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",[]
politics,"A bill passage was passed by Congress impacting New Delhi, India.","[('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Cristiano Ronaldo led Team India to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The uprising took place in Rome, Italy and involved Roman Senate.","[('Roman Senate', 'PERSON')]"
sports,NBA announced a new final match for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The coronation took place in Delhi, India and involved Roman Senate.","[('Roman Senate', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"M.S. Dhoni led NBA to victory at the season opener in Melbourne, Australia.","[('NBA', 'ORG')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on climate study at Harvard University.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
science,A study on gene sequencing led by Albert Einstein was published on 1960-05-22.,"[('1960', 'DATE'), ('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Vincent van Gogh exhibited a new opera at Louvre Museum.,"[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The final match in Melbourne, Australia featured Serena Williams and Team India.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
business,Siemens acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $15M.,[]
technology,IBM released a AI-driven sensors that improves quantum computing.,"[('IBM', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Metropolitan Opera announced restoration of the symphony in New York, USA.","[('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Goldman Sachs following the acquisition.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
arts,Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new installation at Sydney Opera House.,"[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"Serena Williams led Team India to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of yield improvement study in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The Treaty signing took place in Constantinople, Turkey and involved Mughal Empire.","[('The Treaty', 'PERSON'), ('Mughal Empire', 'PERSON')]"
technology,OpenAI released a 5G networks that improves robotics.,[]
agriculture,"Farmers in Iowa, USA adopted pest control trial developed by ICAR.","[('USA', 'ORG'), ('ICAR', 'ORG')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on gene sequencing at CERN.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
science,Harvard University announced a climate study that impacts climatology.,"[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
arts,Vincent van Gogh exhibited a new installation at Sydney Opera House.,"[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Beyoncé is housed in Sydney Opera House in Paris, France.","[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"International Rice Research Institute introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Punjab, India.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Leonardo da Vinci premiered a exhibition at New York, USA.","[('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
sports,NBA announced a new final match for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
arts,Beyoncé exhibited a new symphony at Sydney Opera House.,"[('Sydney Opera House', 'PERSON')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on particle discovery at NASA.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Frida Kahlo premiered a symphony at Madrid, Spain.","[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous painting by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Louvre Museum in Madrid, Spain.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Punjab, India adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by AgriTech Ltd.",[]
technology,A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by Apple.,"[('Apple', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for maize.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The expedition took place in Rome, Italy and involved Mughal Empire.","[('Mughal Empire', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Reliance Industries following the restructuring.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Norman Borlaug led trials of pest control trial in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Angela Merkel met leaders from United Nations in Washington, USA to discuss summit.","[('Angela Merkel', 'PERSON'), ('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show coronation happened in Berlin, Germany around 1987-01-02.","[('1987', 'DATE')]"
sports,"Serena Williams led Team India to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The uprising marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",[]
agriculture,A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.,"[('Wangari Maathai', 'PERSON')]"
science,Albert Einstein published findings on field research at CERN.,"[('Albert Einstein', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The final match in London, UK featured Lionel Messi and Team India.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
history,Cleopatra was a key figure in the uprising.,[]
sports,"The tournament in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and FC Barcelona.","[('UK', 'ORG'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding climate at New Delhi, India.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Narendra Modi met leaders from Parliament in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss bill passage.","[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"FAO introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('FAO', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on field research led by Marie Curie was published on 1902-12-07.,"[('1902', 'DATE'), ('Marie Curie', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Beyoncé exhibited a new installation at Metropolitan Opera.,"[('Metropolitan Opera', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of pest control trial for maize.,[]
sports,"Lionel Messi led Wimbledon to victory at the season opener in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON')]"
business,IPO led to restructuring at Tesla.,"[('IPO', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding trade at Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
science,"Researchers at Harvard University reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,"Reliance Industries opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand financial services.","[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google released a AI-driven sensors that improves edge computing.,"[('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
science,Jane Goodall published findings on gene sequencing at Max Planck Institute.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON'), ('Institute', 'ORG')]"
arts,"A famous installation by Leonardo da Vinci is housed in Tate Modern in New York, USA.","[('Tate Modern', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Farmers in Iowa, USA adopted pest control trial developed by CIMMYT.","[('USA', 'ORG'), ('CIMMYT', 'ORG')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Frida Kahlo is housed in Tate Modern in Vienna, Austria.","[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON'), ('Tate Modern', 'PERSON')]"
history,Cleopatra was a key figure in the battle.,[]
sports,"The tournament in Melbourne, Australia featured Lionel Messi and Team India.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by George Washington Carver showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.,"[('George Washington Carver', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Louvre Museum announced restoration of the opera in Vienna, Austria.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Royal Academy announced restoration of the painting in Madrid, Spain.","[('Royal Academy', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in robotics was reported by Microsoft.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
science,Jane Goodall published findings on particle discovery at NASA.,"[('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
business,"Siemens opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand consumer electronics.",[]
business,"Reliance Industries opened a new office in New York, USA to expand consumer electronics.","[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A policy announcement was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.","[('United Nations', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a field research in Geneva, Switzerland.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show uprising happened in Delhi, India around 1923-05-02.","[('1923', 'DATE')]"
business,Sundar Pichai became CEO of Tesla following the restructuring.,"[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
technology,OpenAI released a edge computing that improves AI-driven sensors.,"[('AI', 'ORG')]"
sports,"Cristiano Ronaldo led Wimbledon to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
technology,A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by OpenAI.,[]
science,Max Planck Institute announced a field research that impacts genetics.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
sports,"Lionel Messi led NBA to victory at the tournament in London, UK.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Ludwig van Beethoven premiered a symphony at Vienna, Austria.",[]
arts,"Frida Kahlo premiered a symphony at Vienna, Austria.","[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous exhibition by Beyoncé is housed in Louvre Museum in Paris, France.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new final match for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
agriculture,"AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Punjab, India.",[]
technology,A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by Google.,"[('Google', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"International Rice Research Institute introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Punjab, India.","[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
politics,"A summit was passed by Congress impacting Washington, USA.","[('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Apple released a robotics that improves AI-driven sensors.,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"Norman Borlaug led trials of yield improvement study in Nairobi, Kenya.","[('Norman Borlaug', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Frida Kahlo premiered a painting at Vienna, Austria.","[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of yield improvement study for rice.,[]
agriculture,A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.,[]
history,"The uprising marked a turning point in Rome, Italy's history.",[]
sports,"M.S. Dhoni led NBA to victory at the final match in London, UK.","[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Ludwig van Beethoven premiered a exhibition at New York, USA.","[('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
technology,A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by SpaceX.,[]
science,A study on field research led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1733-08-03.,"[('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Elon Musk led the launch of a quantum computing in Bengaluru, India.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from United Nations in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss summit.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('United Nations', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Pablo Picasso exhibited a new exhibition at Royal Academy.,"[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('Royal Academy', 'PERSON')]"
agriculture,"Rachel Carson led trials of yield improvement study in Punjab, India.","[('Rachel Carson', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"A famous symphony by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Royal Academy in Paris, France.","[('Royal Academy', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
science,Max Planck Institute announced a gene sequencing that impacts physics.,"[('Institute', 'ORG')]"
arts,"Louvre Museum announced restoration of the symphony in New York, USA.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
agriculture,"M. S. Swaminathan led trials of yield improvement study in Lima, Peru.",[]
science,Marie Curie published findings on particle discovery at Harvard University.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from Congress in New Delhi, India to discuss bill passage.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
business,"Tesla opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand consumer electronics.","[('South Korea', 'PERSON')]"
arts,"Beyoncé premiered a painting at Madrid, Spain.",[]
arts,"A famous exhibition by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Louvre Museum in New York, USA.","[('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,"The Treaty signing took place in Berlin, Germany and involved British Empire.","[('The Treaty', 'PERSON'), ('British Empire', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Pablo Picasso exhibited a new opera at Louvre Museum.,"[('Pablo Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The battle marked a turning point in Constantinople, Turkey's history.",[]
sports,NBA announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('2023', 'DATE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
history,"Records show coronation happened in Delhi, India around 1674-10-24.",[]
sports,FC Barcelona announced a new tournament for 2024-2025.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('FC', 'ORG')]"
science,A study on climate study led by Marie Curie was published on 1575-11-05.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON')]"
arts,Frida Kahlo exhibited a new exhibition at Louvre Museum.,"[('Frida Kahlo', 'PERSON'), ('Louvre Museum', 'PERSON')]"
sports,Team India announced a new tournament for 2023-2024.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('2024', 'DATE'), ('Team India', 'PERSON')]"
science,Marie Curie published findings on climate study at CERN.,"[('Marie Curie', 'PERSON'), ('CERN', 'ORG')]"
sports,"The final match in Madrid, Spain featured Lionel Messi and Wimbledon.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON')]"
history,"Records show expedition happened in Berlin, Germany around 1511-04-02.",[]
sports,"Lionel Messi led NBA to victory at the final match in Madrid, Spain.","[('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
science,"Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a particle discovery in Cape Town, South Africa.","[('Cape Town', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'PERSON'), ('Institute', 'ORG')]"
science,Harvard University announced a particle discovery that impacts physics.,"[('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG')]"
business,Tesla acquired Samsung in a deal valued at $15M.,[]
science,A study on climate study led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1619-08-15.,"[('Rosalind Franklin', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Sundar Pichai led the launch of a quantum computing in Shenzhen, China.","[('Sundar Pichai', 'PERSON')]"
history,"The expedition took place in Constantinople, Turkey and involved British Empire.","[('British Empire', 'PERSON')]"
technology,SpaceX released a quantum computing that improves AI-driven sensors.,"[('AI', 'ORG')]"
politics,"Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'ORG')]"
history,Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the Treaty signing.,"[('Mahatma Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
sports,"The tournament in Melbourne, Australia featured Cristiano Ronaldo and Wimbledon.","[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
science,A study on field research led by Jane Goodall was published on 2006-12-09.,"[('2006', 'DATE'), ('Jane Goodall', 'PERSON')]"
science,"Researchers at NASA reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.","[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'ORG')]"
business,Indra Nooyi became CEO of Samsung following the acquisition.,"[('Indra Nooyi', 'PERSON'), ('CEO', 'ORG')]"
business,Reliance Industries acquired Siemens in a deal valued at $1.2B.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON')]"
politics,"Kamala Harris met leaders from Parliament in New Delhi, India to discuss policy announcement.","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'PERSON')]"
business,Goldman Sachs acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $450M.,"[('Reliance Industries', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
