domain,text,entities
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Oxford University', 'ORG'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('the Mayo Clinic', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('last quarter', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon Web Services', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
Education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('John Hopkins University', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('JP Morgan Chase', 'ORG'), ('June 2022', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Copilot', 'ORG'), ('Windows 11', 'LAW'), ('September 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('The University of Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('July 2022', 'DATE')]"
Health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('August 2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('2022', 'DATE')]"
Finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('2021', 'DATE')]"
Education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG'), ('last December', 'DATE')]"
Finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('The Reserve Bank of India', 'ORG'), ('April 2023', 'DATE')]"
Health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('March 2021', 'DATE')]"
