domain,text,entities
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its holdings in Apple last year.,"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Dr. Alan Walker presented a paper on climate change at Oxford University in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('Alan Walker', 'PERSON'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,"Apple Inc. released the iPhone 15 on October 15, 2023.","[('2023', 'DATE'), ('October 15, 2023', 'DATE'), ('Inc', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Sarah Johnson conducted a study on diabetes in 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Dr. Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Sarah Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
health,Dr. Emily Carter joined the Mayo Clinic as a senior surgeon last year.,"[('Dr. Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Emily Carter', 'PERSON'), ('Mayo Clinic', 'PERSON')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
finance,Goldman Sachs reported a 10% rise in revenue last quarter.,"[('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Amazon Web Services launched new cloud infrastructure in India last year.,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Services', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
technology,Google partnered with NASA to advance quantum computing in 2024.,"[('2024', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
education,MIT announced new scholarships for data science students in 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
health,John Hopkins University reported an increase in mental health cases in 2020.,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('John Hopkins', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
education,"Harvard University launched a new AI program on June 10, 2024.","[('2024', 'DATE'), ('June 10, 2024', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,JP Morgan Chase acquired a fintech startup in June 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Chase', 'PERSON'), ('JP', 'ORG')]"
technology,Microsoft introduced Copilot features to Windows 11 in September 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,The University of Cambridge held its annual convocation in July 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('July', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG')]"
health,Pfizer announced a new vaccine trial in August 2022.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
technology,Elon Musk unveiled the new Tesla chip during a 2022 event.,"[('2022', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
finance,"Elon Musk invested in Bitcoin in 2021, influencing global markets.","[('2021', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
education,Stanford University collaborated with Google on an AI ethics project last December.,"[('December', 'DATE'), ('University', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
finance,The Reserve Bank of India announced new monetary policies in April 2023.,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bank', 'ORG')]"
health,The World Health Organization released new COVID-19 guidelines in March 2021.,"[('2021', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]"
